In this clip we will talk a little bit more how to use our handkerchiefs.
You can use one or two.
It depends of the decision or the mood or the master, technique also.
So the rotation again, uses the same cycle of one, two, three; one, two, three; one, two, three.
Going outward to concentric circles or inward; one, two, three; one, two, three; one, two, three; one, two, three.
Or, one, two, three; one, two, three; one, two, three.
Again, rising and falling.
One, two, three; one, two, three; one, two, three; one, two, three.
It's very similar to the movement of the hands from rising up and one hand or two hands.
But, it's a little bit difficult to combine the basic step with the movement of the arms.
And, one, two, three; one, two, three, because the movement of the arms is continuous, there is no rhythm in it.
One, two, three; one, two, three; one, two, three; one, two, three.